Previously on "desperate housewives,"
前情提要
as one affair ends...
(一段情事告终)
we don't have to sneak around anymore.
我们不用再偷偷摸摸的了
We can have a real relationship.
我们的关系可以光明正大了
Another begins.
- (一段新的开始上演)
Edie!
Edie
I had asked her if she'd like to live together,
我问她愿不愿意跟我同居 她答应了
And yet another...
(而另一段情事...）
this is rex's motherphyllis.
这位是Rex的母亲 Phyllis
Claims.This is joe flannery.
保险索赔部 我是Joe Flannery
Are you awarethat my daughter-in-law has a boyfriend?
你知道我的儿媳有个男友么
Is exposed.
(终被曝光）
It's not going to break your heart to leave those sad,little faces behind?
看着那一张张伤心的小脸你能舍得么
And while some people can't wait to get out of the house,
(在一些人迫不及待走出家门的同时）
others are being kept there,
(另一些人却被强迫 囚禁家中）
against their will.
Now which oneis rex's headstone?
哪个是Rex的墓碑 我总是忘
I always forget.
It's right down this row.
就在这排
Oh. Oh,yes.
哦 哦是 对
That's right.
哦 哦是 对 (这些年来 Bree van de Kamp愈发担心她婆婆的记性）
Over the years,bree van de kamp had grown increasingly concerned
(这些年来 Bree van de Kamp愈发担心她婆婆的记性）
over her mother-in-law's forgetfulness.
Oh,honey,did I forget to takethe pins out of that dress?
哦 甜心 我忘了把针拿下来了是么
Her lapses had become more frequent...
(她的健忘越来越频繁...)
sweetie,didn't I tell youI was going to paint that chair?
宝贝儿 我没告诉你我要给椅子上漆么
More glaring...
(越来越严重...)
oh,dear. Didn't I mentionI waxed the floor?
哦 亲爱的 我没说过我给地板打过蜡了么
And more dangerous.
(越来越危险）
Yes,bree was worried about phyllis' faulty memory,
(是的 Bree担心Phyllis要命的记性）
but she was more than happy to remind her,
(但她乐得提醒她）
especially when it came to the important things.
(尤其是那些重要的事情）
So have you given any thought to when you might be endingyour visit?
你有没有打算过要什么时候走呢
- What?
- 怎么了
Have I become a burden?
我住这烦扰到你了么
Is that what you're saying?
你是这个意思么
I was simply askingwhen you were planning to leave.
我就是随便问问你打算什么时候走
There was no agendabehind the question.
我的问题什么目的都没有
Oh. I-I don't know.
哦 我..不知道
Why don't we play it by ear?
看情况再说吧
Yes,let'S.
嗯 好吧
What on earth?
- 这是什么啊
Oh,my god.
天那
What happened?
这是怎么啦
It looks like someonedug rex up.
看来好像有人把rex挖出来了
Well,I got that,but why?
是啊我看出来了 但为什么啊
Why would they do that?
他们为什么要这样
I don't know.
不知道
Unless...
除非...
unless what?
除非什么
Maybe this has something to do with thatinsurance investigator.
除非这跟那个保险调查员有关
Insurance investigator?
- 保险调查员？
He came by askingall sorts of questions.
他上门来问了好多问题
I don't know whatyou're talking about,phyllis.
我不知道你在说什么 Phyllis
Maybe you were at the store.
你可能在商店呢
Anyway,he was very suspicious.
总之 他觉得事有蹊跷
Suspicious?
- 蹊跷？
Oh,yes. He has a theory that rex didn't dieof a heart attack.
嗯 是啊。他觉得rex不是死于心脏病的
He thinks he was poisoned.
他认为他是被毒死的
It was in that moment bree could finally see the truth.
(就在这一刻 Bree终于明白了)
Did I not mention that?
我又忘了说么
Her mother-in-law's memory was fine.
(她婆婆的记性并没问题）
It was her soul that was faulty.
(要命的是她的心眼）
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=- Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园论坛 http://www.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync:YTET-fisherchen -=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
-=COSL-YTET小组工作室=- 翻译: 七宝 少数派 ronalds 校对：少数派 ronalds 时间轴: fisherchen
The parties took place on the front lawn of 4347 wisteria lane
(聚会每周日下午在Wisteria Lane 4347号草坪上举行)
every sunday afternoon.
Chloe pendergast would bring the tea set,
(Chloe pendergast会带来茶具）
which was appropriate,
(这无可厚非 因为她是女主人）
since she was the hostess.
Brittany chries provided formal attire from her mother's closet.
(Brittany chries提供服装 均出自妈妈的衣柜）
And marissa anne mckay invited the additional guests,
(而marissa anne mckay带来其余的客人）
some of whom hadn't been to a party in years.
(其中有些人有年头没参加聚会了）
Of course,it never occurred to the three young girls
(自然 三个小女孩没发现 ）
that while they were busy playing out their fantasy,
(当她们忙着聚会幻想的时候）
one of the older girls in the neighborhood
(邻居家里的一个大女孩 也在享受着自己的幻想）
was engaging in a fantasy of her own.
- hey...
- 嗨
oh,hi,mrs. Solis.
哦 嗨 Solis太太
- Ralph.
- 你好Ralph
Off to the mall again?
又去逛街么
You know me.
你真了解我
There was nothing gabrielle enjoyed as much as shopping.
(没有什么比购物更让gabrielle高兴的了）
And even when she couldn't afford to take anything home,
(而当她负担不起带东西回家的时候）
she took satisfaction in looking...
(她满足于只是观赏...）
at the merchandise.
(商品）
Hey,susan.
嗨 Susan 怎么了
What's goin' on?
It's karl's weekend to have julie,
周末julie都和karl过 他们总是6点回来的
and they're always back by 6.
That's our custody agreement,
这是我们的监护协议 6点回来 现在已经过了6点了
back by 6,and it's after 6.
It's like 6:15.
- 刚6点15
Well,see?There you go.
是啊 你看 晚了吧
I'm sure they just forgot.
他们肯定只是忘了
Well,I have a court order.
这是法庭要求 我没办法
It's out of my hands.
Yeah,it'd still be nice if you gave him a grace period.
是啊 但你要是能赦免这么一次不是很好么
Oh,I'm being nice.
我已经很好了 就差拘捕他了
I could have him arrested.
I mean,don't get me wrong.
我是说 别误会我 我愿意julie和Karl在一起
I am all for julie spending time with karl.
He is still her dad,
他毕竟是他父亲 而且她爱他
and she loves him.
But...
- 但是...
but he's with edie.
- 但是他跟edie在一起
I mean,she's not exactly the maternal type.
她可不是很母性的类型
I wouldn't be a good mother if I wasn't concerned.
我要不担心我就不是个好母亲
I mean,who knows what passes for a kid-friendly,
谁知道他们在里边怎么度过亲子时光呢
good time in there?
Drugs? Porn? Smoking?
嗑药？A片？抽烟？
doesn't sound like they're having an orgy in there.
听起来里面不像是在放肆狂欢
obviously,they saw us coming.
很明显 他们知道咱们要来
whoo! That's a strike!
喔 扔的好
Hey,guys!
- 嗨
Hey! Look who's here!
嗨 看谁回来了
Parker,guess what I got.
- parker 猜我买什么了
What?
什么
School supplies.
- 文具！
School supplies?!
文具？
Yeah,and the best part of it is I got you a really cool backpack.
而且里面最棒的是... 我给你买了 一个酷毙的背包
Whoa,look at that.
哇 看看 很棒吧？
Pretty neat,huh?
Wow. Thanks.
哇 谢谢
So on your first day of school,
第一天上学的时候 你和你爸爸可以找到你的小柜子
you and your dad can find your cubby and you can hang it up.
第一天上学的时候 你和你爸爸可以找到你的小柜子 然后挂上它
You're not taking me?
你不送我去？
Actually,your dad's going to take you to school on your first day.
第一天上学你爸爸会送你去
Yeah,just me and you,big guy.
对 就我和你 小伙子 我会领着你的手带你进去的
I'll be right there to hold your hand.
But I thought mommy was taking me.
- 但我以为妈妈会带我去的
Yeah,well,honey,I have to work.
- 是啊 宝贝 妈妈要工作啊
Mommy's boss is a mean,mean lady and if I miss work,
妈妈的老板是个小气的女人
I'll lose my job and then we won't have any money to buy food.
如果我不去上班 我就会被炒 我们就没钱买吃的了
Honey,you gotta believe me,
宝贝 你要相信我
if I could be there,you know that I would.
如果我能去 你知道我一定会去得
all right,I didn't know it was that important to you.
好吧 我不知道你这么在乎这个
I will talk to my boss and I will see what I can do.
我会和我老板谈谈 看看怎么办
Thank you,mommy.
谢谢 妈咪
Wow,I don't want to rain on your parade,
喔 我不想破你冷水 但完全你被他玩弄于股掌了
but he just totally manipulated you.
Well,hey,when a kid'sthat good,you gotta give him his due.
是啊 孩子那么听话的时候 你应该满足他
An autopsy?
验尸? 探长 rex是心脏病发而死的
Detective,rex diedof a heart attack.
Well,there weresome anomalies in the doctor's report.
- 在医生的报告里有一些反常
Anomalies?What anomalies?
- 反常? 什么反常
Ma'am,I'm afraidI'm not at liberty to discuss thisany further with you.
女士 恐怕我不是很方便跟你透漏这些
Am I a suspect?
- 我成了嫌犯么？
I didn't say that.
我没那么说
Well,if I am,you're wasting your time.
要是的话 你就在浪费时间了
I loved rex and anyonewho knows me will tell you
我爱rex 了解我的人都会告诉你我根本不会伤害他的
that I was incapableof hurting him.
You sure about that?
你确定么？
You talked to phyllis.
- 你和phyllis谈过
Again,I can't discussthe case.
再说一次 我不能透露
She's my mother-in-law.
- 她是我婆婆
Of course she saidhorrible things about me.
她当然会说我的坏话
Ma'am,lower your voice.
女士 请你小点声
She blamed me for every problemthat rex and I ever had.
她把我和rex的所有问题都怪罪在我头上
So there were problems with the marriage?
- 这么说婚姻中有问题咯
Well,it was a marriage. Of course there were problems.
这是婚姻阿 当然有些问题
May I record this just so there's no confusion
我能不能录下来你得话 以防以后出现误会
over your statement?
以防以后出现误会
No,you may not record this.
- 不能 你不许录音
So you refuse to make a statement?
这么说你拒绝供诉
I'm not refusing anything.
我没拒绝什么
All I'm saying is stay away from phyllis.
我只是说让你别听phyllis的
She's a--she's a raving loon.
她...她是个发癫的蠢人
Ma'am,perhaps you'd bemore comfortable with an attorney present.
女士 或许有个律师在场会更合适
You want a statement?Fine,I'll give you a statement.
你想要口供？ 好 我就给你口供
My husband diedof a heart attack.
我的丈夫死于心脏病 我很爱他
I loved him very deeply,
and your motherdid a lousy job.
另外 你母亲没教育好你
To bree's way of thinking,
(在Bree看来）
there were two kinds of people in the world--
(世界上有两种人）
those who were useless before their morning coffee...
(一种是在喝到清晨咖啡之前等同废人）
and those who weren'T.
(一种却正好相反）
What's going on?
发生什么了
Don't rush me,bree!
别推我 bree 我很老了
I'm an old woman!Don't rush me.
Get her out of here.
把-她-带-走！
I will tell you one thing--
我告诉你吧
you wouldn't be actingthis way
你要不是觉得有罪恶感你不会这样的
if you didn't feel guiltyabout something!
what's the occasion?
什么节日？
Uh,our anniversary?
啊 我们结婚周年
Oh,right.
哦 对
How could you forgetour anniversary?
你怎么把结婚纪念日都忘了
You sit in a cell all day longstaring at a calendar.
你在牢房里天天盯着日历
What's the big deal?
有什么大不了的 我们的婚姻不过是个假相
Our marriagewas a sham anyway.
Oh,we're not doing this again.
- 哦 别又来这套
In real marriages,wives are faithful.
妻子是忠贞的
Yeah,and husbands remember anniversaries,
是啊 而且丈夫会记得纪念日
so I guess we're even.
所以我们平了
Are you equating forgetting our anniversary with cheating on me?
忘记纪念日和偷情能相当么
You are clearly determined to ruin this special day for us.
你一心想毁掉这个特别的日子
What is wrong with you that you don't feel guilty?
- 你怎么就不觉得愧疚呢
I feel tons of guilt,so back off.
- 我愧疚得很 别没完！
You never even apologized.
- 你从来没道歉过
I apologized a million times.
我都道了100万次歉
Yeah,but you always followedit up with an excuse.
是啊 但后面总是带着一个借口
"I was lonely,you weren't home enough,
"我很孤独 你总不在家 女人需要被爱"
a woman needs to be loved."
A womandoes need to be loved,
女人需要被爱 既然你不给 我就到别处去找
and since you didn'tgive it to me,
I had to find it elsewhere.
女人需要被爱 既然你不给 我就到别处去找
So that's what the teenagerwas doing in our bedroom--
这就是那个小屁孩在我们卧室作的？
filling you with love.
给你关爱？
Say what you want,
随便你怎么说 但John Rowland对我的爱是最真的
but john rowland loved melike no one ever has.
Not as a trophyor as a possession,but for me.
不把我当战利品 或者所有物 而是爱我的人
He loved me.
他爱我
no,he really did.
真的 他真的爱我
Let me count the ways.
唔 让我想想他如何爱我的
Um,gently,savagely,
温柔的 狂野的 频繁的 倒立式的...
frequently,upside down...
is there a problem here?
出了什么问题么
No,it's our anniversary.
没 今天是我们的周年纪念
We're just relivingthe good times.
我们在回忆好时光
That's an amazing car.Aston martin,right?
- 这车真棒 阿斯顿马丁吧？
Uh-huh. Brand-new.Limited edition.
对 全新的 限量版
A little anniversary presentfrom my husband.
我丈夫给的周年纪念礼物
He's very generous.
- 他可真大方
More than he knows.
- 他自己都不知道
I'm sorry. What?
- 不好意思 你说什么
I'm singing at church for the family follies.
我要在教堂为家庭讽刺剧唱歌
Edie's going to accompany meon guitar.
Edie要为我弹吉它 她弹得不赖
She's really good.
So you and edieare going to be an act.
你和Edie演出一个节目？
Is that a problem?
- 怎么了
No. No. I mean,I'm a little surprised that you didn't ask meto accompany you first.
- 没 没，我是有些意外你没先来找我给你伴奏
On what?
- 用什么
You don't play an instrument.
你又不会乐器
I play the piano.You know that.
- 我会钢琴 你知道的
How would I know that? I've never seen you play.
- 我怎么知道 没看你弹过
Well,I played in high school.
我在高中时候弹得
So the last time you tickled the ivories was sometimein the late '70s?
这么说你上次摸琴是70年代末了
It was the early '80s.
80年代初
Well,I'm not goingto argue with you.
行了 我不和你争
You want to do the show with edie,
你要和Edie表演
and I think that's super.
我觉得好极了
So she's really good,huh?
她弹得很好？
She knows her guitar.
她弹得不赖
Apparently,there are a lotof musicians in her family,
原来她家里有很多音乐家
sort of likethe von trapps.
就像Von Trapps
Except,you know,her brother od'D.
除了她哥服毒过量死了
All I'm asking you is to go out and play a little bit of ball.
我只是想走出屋子 玩玩球
Is that such a big deal?
有什么大不了的
Matthew,you are such an excellent player,darling,
Matthew 你球玩得太好了宝贝儿
that people will want to be your friend.
别人会想认识你得
Then next thing you know,
一来二去
god knows who will be wanting to drop by and calling.
天知道谁会想要来拜访或者打电话
Sweetie,we need to keep a low profile.
甜心 我们要保持低调
Yeah,I know,
是的 我知道
but I have got to get outof this house sometime.
但我得不时除去转转
I'm going crazy here,okay?
我在家要发疯了 好么
What is it?
干什么
Oh,my daughter is singinga song at church
哦 我女儿要在教堂唱歌
and I want to accompany heron the piano
我想给她作钢琴伴奏
and I haven't played in years.
我好久没弹过了
Oh,you were just so amazing at rex's funeral the other day,
那天你在rex的葬礼上弹得太美了
I was wondering
- 我就在想...
I don't give lessons.
我不教人的
Oh. Oh,okay.
哦 好吧
Oh. You have a little,uh,on your...
哦 你有点...在你...
I'm baking cherry pie.Excuse me.
我在做樱桃派 抱歉
What happened to maintaining a low profile?
你还怎么保持低调
You keep being rude to everybody,
你对每个人都那么不友好
they're gonna start whispering about us.
他们会谈论我们的
You're right.
你说得对
We do want to fit in.
我们得和大家融洽点
Lynette,check it out.
Lynette 看
Jason's mouth.
jason的嘴
Stu,isn't that the newvideo conference setup?
- Stu 这是那个新的视频会议系统么
Yeah. Isn't the resolutionfantastic?
对 这个东西妙极了吧
Hey,nina.
- 嗨 Nina
Mm-hmm?
唔？
Uh,about tomorrow morning...
- 关于明天早上...
mm-hmm?
唔？
You know how the first hourof the morning meeting is always so slow?
你知道清晨会议的头一个小时总是进行的很慢
'Cause I've got this thing...
我有点事...
good god,this is notabout your kids again,is it?
上帝 不是又关于你得孩子吧
I know,I promisedI wouldn't do this,
我知道 我保证过我不会这样
but parker really needs meto be there on his first dayof kindergarten.
但Parker第一天幼儿园真的需要我在
He's so freaked outI can't be there.
- 我不能去让他发慌了
I'm sorry. How is thismy problem?
不好意思 这跟我有什么关系
Because we can't escapethe fact that I have kids.
因为我们不能忽略我有孩子的事实
I love my job,but to be fair,
我爱我的工作 但公平点说
there's gotta be some balance.
这可以有一个平衡的
Okay,how about the peoplethat don't have the kids?
好吧 那那些没有孩子的人呢
Did you ever considerthat they might need a little more balancein their lives,hmm?
你有考虑过他们生活中是不是也需要一点平衡呢
Like,maybe they wantto go see a matinee
比如 也许他们想去看演出
or perhaps they wantto come in a little late
或者他们玩了一夜想晚点上班
after a big crazy night out
or maybe they justwant to get a hair cut,
或者他们只是想剪个头发
which I,myself,have notbeen able to do for two months.
我本人两个月都没有剪头了
So,no,this is about fairness to the people who arechildless by choice,okay?
所以 抱歉 我要对没有孩子的人公平 好么
Okay. Good point.
好吧 有道理
And I'm sorry about your hair.
我为你的头发感到抱歉
I can see why you're upset.
难怪你这么不高兴
Not now,stu.
别烦我 Stu
Hang on a sec.
等等
I don't understand.
我不明白
This system is gonna letmommy be with you on your first day of school.
这个系统能让妈妈看见你第一天入学的情况
The resolution is fantastic.
这东西妙极了
The next day,
(第二天)
gabrielle decided to cheer herself up
(Gabrielle决定再来一次橱窗浏览)
with another round of window shopping.
(好让自己开心一点）
But this time,she was taken aback
(但这次 她对橱窗里展示的东西吃惊不小）
by what was on display.
Mrs. Tilman.
- Tilman太太
Mr. Delfino.
Delfino先生
I,uh,heard you wereback from the hospital,
我...听说你从医院回来了 所以我带来了这个
so I brought you these.
Oh,I can't tell youhow long it's been
哦 我上一次收到俊男的花不知道是什么时候了
since I got flowersfrom a handsome man.
I mean,I could,but I don't want your pity.
我能记得 但不想让你觉得我可怜
Where are you off to?
你要去哪
I'm going back to utahfor a few weeks.
我要回尤他州一阵
The recuperation'staking longer than the doctors anticipated.
恢复比医生预计的长了一些
Speaking of my attack,
说道我被打的事
have they caughtyoung zachary yet?
他们抓到Zachary了么
No,actually,that's why I'm here.
没有 事实上这就是我来的原因
So the flowerswere just a ruse.
那这些花只是个计策 明白了
Figures.I'm trying to find zach before he gets inany more trouble.
我想在zach再惹出麻烦之前找到他
Do you know any friendsthat he might have,
你知道他是否有些什么朋友 或者他有什么藏身的地方？
anywhere he might be holed up?
I know you were close to him.
我知道你和他比较亲近
Funny thing,since he beat meand threw me down the stairs,
真逗 自从他打了我把我推下楼梯以后 我们就不怎么联络了
we just don't stay in touchlike we should.
Since when do you careso much about zach young?
你什么时候开始那么关心Zach Young了
It's complicated.
- 情况很复杂
I'll bet.
- 我估计也是
I'm sure he's out theresomewhere trying to find his father,
我肯定他在外面到处找他的爸爸
which I trust you madeimpossible.
而你让这成为不可能了
No,I let paul go.
不 我放了Paul 我下不了手
I couldn'tgo through with it.
That was a mistake.
你犯了个错误
He will spendthe rest of his life running from the police.
他的余生都要四处躲藏了 这算是惩罚他了
I think that'spunishment enough.
Zach is the only connection that paul haswith his dead wife.
Zach是他和他亡妻的唯一牵连
At some point,he will runback here looking for him.
说不定他会跑回来找zach
I don't like to be negative,
我不喜欢消极看事情 但你真该杀了他的
but you really should havekilled him.
At the risk of ruininga lovely evening,
冒着糟蹋一个美好夜晚的危险
I have some unpleasant news.
The police dug upyour father today.
我有一个不太好的消息 警察今天把你们的父亲挖出来了
What?Why?
- 什么 为什么
Well,apparently,they want to do an autopsy.
很显然 他们想要验尸
They don't thinkthat he had a heart attack.
他们认为他不是死于心脏病 他们觉得有人给他下毒
They think that somebodywas poisoning him.
Who would havepoisoned daddy?
- 谁会给爸爸下毒？
Well,apparently,I'm a suspect.
- 显然我是嫌疑犯
Well,they always lookat spouses first.
他们总是先怀疑配偶的
It has something to dowith statistics.
这是他们的一贯手法
It's just a formality.I'll be cleared in no time.
只是走一个过程 我很快就会澄清
Would you two pleasestop looking at me like that?
你们俩能别这么看着我么 你们清楚我没杀你们父亲
Obviously,I did notkill your father.
I loved him deeply.
我爱他很深
Yeah,but you and dadhad a lot of problems.
是啊 但你和爸爸问题很多 人人都知道
Everyone knows that.
Yes,we had issues,but I would never have hurt him.
是的 我们有些问题 但我永远不会伤害他的
What about the night daddyhad his second heart attack?
那爸爸第二次心脏病发作那晚呢
You must have loved hima lot to make the bed before takinghim to the hospital.
你带他去医院之前还要整理床铺 可真够爱他的
I was in shock,danielle.You know that.
我当时慌了 Danielle 你很清楚
Andrew,surely you don't thinkI murdered your father.
Andrew 我肯定你没认为我杀了你父亲吧
I know you didn'T.
我知道不是你 你不会杀人的
You're not capable of murder.
Thank you.
谢谢
That wasn't a compliment.
我没在夸奖你
It takes gutsto kill somebody.
有种的人才敢杀人
Thank you so much for changingyour mind about helping me.
谢谢你能改主意帮助我 感激不尽
I really appreciate it.
I'm happy to help...
我乐于帮忙
and I'm sorry if I seemedrude before.
如果我之前有些无礼请见谅
I-I was having a bad day.
我当时心情不好
That's good.
不错 弹得不错 最好不要过度拉长持续音
That's really good.
You might want tolay off the pedal.
不错 弹得不错 最好不要过度拉长持续音
Really?
真的么 我以为这样听着更专业呢
Oh,I thought it made it soundmore professional.
It doesn'T.
并不是的
boy,your son really likesto play his hip-hop music loud.
你儿子很喜欢大声听hip-hop阿
The good news is it drownsout the sound of the dryer.
好处是这样就听不到烘干机的声音了
arch your fingers,susan.
手指弓起来
hi.I'm sorry to interrupt.
嗨 不好意思打扰了 我敲门了 我猜你们没听到
I knocked,but I guessyou guys didn't hear me.
We were just hoping that whoeverit was would go away.
不 我们听见了 我们只是期望敲门的人赶快走
I'm still hopingthat'll happen.
我现在也这么期望
What's up,mom?
什么事 妈
Well,I have good news.
我有个好消息
Um,I've been takingpiano lessons with betty applewhite,
我在betty applewhite那里上钢琴课
and,uh,well,I just thoughtmaybe I could join you guys.
所以...我想也许我可以加入你们
You know,like a trio.
- 你们知道 像一个三人组合
Doesn't that sound fun?
听起来很好玩吧
I don't do trios,but thanks anyway.
我不搞三人组合 还是谢谢你了
Well,I don't mean to betechnical here,
我不是想打扰你们 只是这个节目
but this show,
I mean,it really is supposedto be a family thing,
真的本该是一个家庭活动的
and I hate to point out you're not family.
- 不好意思提醒一下你不是家人
No,but I have talent,
我不是 但我有才华
and to most audiences,talent trumps family.
对大多数观众来说 才华重于家庭
Well,what makes you so sureI don't have talent?
你怎么就知道我没有才华呢
Hmm,just a hunch.
就是感觉
Yeah,well,we've allseen your talent,
是啊 我们都知道你的才华了
which is a nice wayof telling you
这是尽量婉转的提醒你为什么不把卧室装上窗帘
why don't you put some curtains on your bedroom window?
Guys...oh,come on,be honest.
- 大家... 哦 得了 说实话
You didn't want any part of this
在知道我参与之前你根本不想管这事的
until you found out that I was involved.
That is so not true!
- 根本不是这么回事
Oh,yes,it is.
哦就是这么回事
It burns you that your own daughter picked me over you.
你的女儿选我而不是你让你冒火了
She did not pick you.
她没选你 她只是没想到我会同意帮忙
It just didn't occur to herthat I would agree to do it.
Well,now she knows,
好 那现在她知道了 她要是能重新选择 她会选我的
and if she had it to doover again,she'd pick me.
No,she wouldn'T.
- 不 她不会
Well,why don'twe put it to a test?
不如我们试试看
Julie,who would you ratherhave play with you?
julie 你想要谁给你伴奏
Oh,no,no,no,no.
- 哦 别别别别
No,it's okay,honey.
没关系的 宝贝儿
Who do you wantto be with you
你想让谁跟你一起表演家庭才艺节目
in the family talent show?
Yes,who do you wantwith you
对 你想让谁跟你一起站在所有人面前
in front ofall of those people?
And remember,it's a church.
记得 这是教堂 他们会来评论你的
They are goingto be judging you.
Ohh... okay.
好吧 首先 你俩都够烂的
Well,first of all,you both suck,
but if I had to choose...
但是如果必须选的话
I guess I'd pick my mom.
我想还是选我妈妈吧
Sorry,edie.
对不起 edie
Fair enough.
算公平
I'd like my pitch pipe back,please.
正音笛请还给我
it was you,wasn't it?
是你干的 是不是
Hello,john.
你好 john 好久不见
Long time,no see.
One of the neighbors sawan aston martin driving away,
有邻居看到一辆阿斯顿马丁开走了
and what do you know?
这不就是么
Well,someone hadto tend to the yard.
某人本该在院子里的
You were busy elsewhere.
你却在别的地方
You saw us?
- 你看见我们了？
Yes,and I have to say she'sold enough to be your mother.
- 对，而且我不得不说她都老得能当你妈了
Hell,she's old enoughto be my mother.
她老得都够当我妈的了
Joan's only 41.
- Joan只有41岁
Joan?!
你叫她joan?
You're calling her joan?!
Why shouldn't I? She's my friend.
- 为什么不能 她是我朋友
I know your friends,
- 我认识你的朋友们
and I have a hunchyou don't do to your friends
我预感你和你朋友不会做我才看到
what I saw you doingto that wrinkly old lady.
和那个皱巴巴的老太太做的事
Okay,so you caught medoing it with somebody else.
好吧 你抓到我和别人做爱了
What's the big deal?
有什么大不了的
You're supposed to be in love with me.
- 你本该爱着我的
How many time sdid you say it?
你多少次在我耳边说你只爱我一个人
How many times did youw hisper in my ear,
"you're the only womanI'll ever love"?
你多少次在我耳边说你只爱我一个人
I don't know. A bunch.
- 我不知道 几次吧
So were you lying to me?
- 这么说你当时是谎话？
Were you just trying to get me into bed?
- 只是想骗我上床？
No,of course not.
不 当然不是
I loved you,but we broke up.
- 我是爱过你 不过我们已经分手了
Yeah,like five minutes ago!
是呀 还不到五分钟呢！
Haven't you ever heard of a mourning period?
难道你都没有悲伤期吗？
I know it seems quick,but I have feelings for her.
我也知道快了点 不过我对她有感觉
In fact,I thinkI may be in love with her.
其实 我觉得我爱上她了
What's the matter?Is it the baby?
怎么了? 是肚子里的孩子吗？
No.
不是
Oh,no,no. It's me.
是我自己
I am beyond stupid.
愚蠢至极
You're not stupid.
- 你不蠢
Oh,no,I am.
- 不 我很蠢
Yesterday,I was still fantasizing that it could work with you,
昨天我还在幻想和你在一起
that a one-bedroom apartment might be cozy.
想像爱屋是多么的温馨
Mrs. Solis,please.
- Solis夫人 别这样
Oh,my god.I almost left my husband for someone who calls memrs. Solis.
我差点就为了一个 叫我Solis夫人的人离开我的丈夫
So are you upset becauseyou want to get back together?
你是不是因为和好的一事不开心？
Because I can break upwith joan.
我可以马上和joan分手
That's okay,sweetie.I'm good.
没关系 亲爱的 我没事
So this is it for us?
我们就这么完了？
'Cause I really feel like weshould end it better than this.
我还以为收场要远比这个来得好呢
Actually,john,given howstupid both of us have been,
其实 John 我们俩都太傻了
this is an entirelyappropriate ending.
这样结束也算是活该吧
mrs. Van de kamp.
Van de kamp夫人 有什么事吗？
What can I do for you?
I would like to submit myselfto a lie detector test
我想做一个测谎实验 洗清嫌疑
to eliminate any uncertainty
about what happenedwith my husband.
我想做一个测谎实验 洗清嫌疑
Are you sure you don'twant a lawyer present?
你确定不要律师在场？
I'll waive all that.
我放弃 不过我要求我的孩子在场
My only stipulationis that I want my children
to be able to see me answer the questions.
我放弃 不过我要求我的孩子在场
I think we can accommodate you.
那好吧
Is your namebree van de kamp?
- 你叫Van de kamp吗？
Yes.
- 是的
Were you married to rex van de kamp?
你是否嫁给Rex Van de Kamp？
yes.
是的
Did you and your husband temporarily separate last year?
- 你和你丈夫去年是否临时分居？
Yes.
是的
Did you kill your husband?
- 你有没有杀你丈夫？
No.
没有
Do you know a man named george williams?
你是否认识一位叫George Williams的人？
Yes.
是的
During your separation from your husband,
在你分居的时候
did you have a relationship with mr. Williams?
你是否和Williams先生交往？
What does that have to do with anything?
这与案子什么关系？
Just yes or no responses,please.
请回答“是”或“不是”
Well,I'm not gonna respondto something that's none of your business.
我可不会回答与你无关的事
Mrs. Van de kamp,
Van de kamp夫人
if you want us to takethis polygraph seriously,
如果你真想做测试
answer the questions we ask,okay?
就必须回答问题 行吗？
Who's george williams?
谁是George Williams？
He's our pharmacist.
我们家的药剂师
During your separation,did you have a relationship
在你分居的时候
with mr. Williams?
你是否和Williams先生交往？
Yes.
是的
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?
你是否爱Williams先生？
What?
什么?!
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?
你是否爱Williams先生？
No.
不爱
Um,I-I was thinkingof something else just then,
我刚才走神了 你再问一遍吧
so why don't you ask methe question again?
Are you in lovewith mr. Williams?
你是否爱Williams先生？
No.
不爱
Did you see that?
你看见了吗？
Yeah,I saw it.
看见了
Hello,susan.
你好 Susan
Are you ready for your lesson?
准备好上课了吗？
Yep,I am.
是的
I think I'm going to make another push for using that pedal.
我打算这次把持续音再好好练练
I think it adds grandeur.
给人一种庄严感
I want to talk to you!
- 我得好好和你谈谈？
I'm busy now.
- 我忙着呢
I cannot believe
不敢相信你不让Edie参加Julie的表演
you kicked edie out of julie's performance!
I did not kick edie out.
不是我不让
Julie made that call.
是Julie自己决定的
Because you played the mom card.
可你摆出妈妈的架子来威胁她
Well,it is a family recital,and edie is not family.
可我们这是家庭活动 Edie不是家里人
One day,she could be.
- 终有一天她会是的
Ohh,don't even joke like that.
别拿这开玩笑
H-how about your plumber/convicted murderer,huh?
你那位水管工兼杀人犯又如何呢？
He seems to keep popping up at "family" events.
我看他不也经常出现在家庭场合嘛
It was not murder,it was manslaughter,
不是谋杀 是过失杀人
and that's totally different.
而且这是两码事
Mike and I aren't even living together,
Mike和我不住在一起
and he cares about julie.
而且他很关心Julie
Well,so does edie,huh?
Edie也是啊
She was really looking forward to performing with julie.
她很希望和Julie一起演出
If you think edie britt cares about anybody other than herself,
如果你天真到认为Edie Britt会关心他人
you are living ina fool's paradise.
我看你是做大头梦
You don't know her the way I do,
你并不了解Edie
and the only reason she's interested in julie
她这么做的唯一目的就是要气我
is to mess with my head.
hey,that's both crazy and self-absorbed.
你的想法简直既疯狂又自私
That's a twofer! Way to go!
一举两得 真有你的 佩服
Whether you choose to believe it or not,
信不信由你
they're both great together,
她们俩配合的很好
and if you don't believe me,ask julie.
你要是不信 可以问Julie
I'm sorry you had to witness that.
让你看见了 真不好意思
Oh,that's okay,hon.
没事
I have lived my share of family knock-down drag-outs.
我们家也有类似的经历
Well,I hope it wasn't as uglyas me and karl.
希望没我们俩这么丢人
You'd be surprised.
谁说不是呢
Parker,honey,can you hear me?
Parker 你能听见我吗？
Tom,why isn't he talking?
Tom 他怎么不说话？
Um,honey,there are a lot of kids here.
这边孩子挺多的
He's a little stressed.
他有点紧张
Parker,say hi,say hi.Mommy?
Parker 打个招呼 打个招呼
Oh,hey,honey,this is so exciting.
嘿 亲爱的
Your first day of school.
第一天上学肯定很兴奋吧
You're going to make so many friends.
你会认识很多新朋友
Lynette,staff meeting,now.
- Lynette 开会 现在
Uh,right,yeah.I'm going to be right there.
好的  我就去
Now. Now,now,now!
现在 现在 现在 现在！
Stu,this coffee,it's cold.
Stu 咖啡冷了
Honey,I'm going to beright back.
亲爱的 我就回来
Mommy? Where are you going?
- 妈妈 你去哪？
Right back.
- 就回来
Mommy,come back!
妈妈 回来！
Okay,let's turn to page five.
好的 我们翻到第五页
Damn. I forgot my prospectus.Any extra copies?
该死 我忘了拿计划书了 大家还要吗？
No? Oh,I'll be right back.
没人 我就回来
Hi,I'm back.How's he doing?
他怎么样了？
Um,um,honey,he's upset
不太好 本来想给你看他的房间的
because he wanted to show you his cubby. You left.
Oh,honey,I'm here.I'm here.
亲爱的 我在这 我在这
You can show meyour cubby now.
现在给我看你的房间
Nina found extra copies.She wants you back now.
Nina找到多余的计划书了 要你立刻回去开会
Okay. I'll be backin two seconds for you.
- 好的 我一会就回来
Mommy! Mommy!Don't go!
- 妈妈 别走啊！
So the big issue hereis second-quarter billing.
大问题就是第二季度的广告促销
Where are you going?
- 你去哪？
Ladies' room.
洗手间
No.Nina,nature is calling.
- Nina 人有三急嘛
Lynette,hold itfor ten minutes.
Lynette 再忍十分钟
We have to get through this.
我们得谈完了
What I'd like to do is trade out the invoicing structure.
我想谈谈这个货品发票结构
Let's take a look at our graphson page ten,please.
我们一起看看第十页的图表
Lynette had been struggling to balance her career
（Lynette一直想平衡事业和家庭）
and her family.
She finally saw an opportunity to tip the scales in her favor
（她终于看到了一次对自己有利的机会）
Instead of badgering clients with invoices
我提议不再拿短期的宣传缠着那些有发票的顾客
on the shorter term campaigns,I say we bill on delivery.
- 而是采取到货付款的方式 好！到货付款
Yes!
好！
Bill on delivery,yes!
好！到货付款 好！
are you having a seizure?
你中风了啊？
No,no,I'm just--I'm very excited.
不是 我只是高兴
It's a really good plan.
真是个好办法
Now,what happenedon the burman account
缅甸帐户的问题就是会计部的 Tina和Ron给人家传去票据副本
is that they were sentduplicate bills
by tina and ronin accounting
缅甸帐户的问题就是会计部的 Tina和Ron给人家传去票据副本
and I'm not pointingany fingers,
我也不是要故意说谁 但是Tina和Ron 看看单子上到处都是...
but tina,ron,
about walking inand seeing all my lines lit up
我也不是要故意说谁 但是Tina和Ron 看看单子上到处都是...
with disgruntled--aah! Ohh! Hot! Hot!
烫死我了 烫死了 烫死了
Help.
帮个忙
Stu! Aah! Aah!
Stu
And that's why we packed youextra cookies
我们给你那么多的曲奇饼干 就是为了让你和新朋友一起吃
so you could share with allyour new friends,remember?
I think we're good to go now,honey.
差不多该走了 亲爱的
You're going to be great,parker.
你会好好表现的 Parker
I love you.
- 我爱你 亲爱的
I love you,too,mommy.
- 我也爱你 妈妈
Bree,hi. What canI do for you?
Bree 你好 有事吗？
Well,for starters,you can help me prove to the police
有啊 你得帮我向警方证明
that we didn't conspireto kill my husband.
我们没有合谋杀死我的丈夫
Okay.
好吧
So because ofthe anomalies in rex's blood,
由于Rex血液中有异常
the police started to wonderif I'd been poisoning rex.
警方就怀疑是我下毒害死Rex
That's absurd.
太荒唐了
Lots of things can causehigh potassium levels--
有很多因素可以导致钾含量过高 肾衰竭 钠含量过低等
renal failure,low sodium.
太荒唐了
Well,that's why I took the polygraph,
所以我才主动要求测谎以示清白
to prove to themthat I was innocent.
Obviously,you passed.
看来你通过了
Sort of.
算是吧
Well,I think the police now have a different theory,
不过警察倒是认为如果不是我自己下的毒
which is if I wasn't poisoningrex on my own,
then maybe you were helping me.
也许你帮了忙
You're kidding.
- 你开玩笑的吧
No,that's why I need youto take the polygraph,too.
没有  所以你也得去测谎
W-what?
什么？
It's the quickest wayto prove to the police
这是证明警方犯错最好的办法
that they're wrong.
I-I don't understand.We're just friends.
我不很明白 我们只是朋友
Why would the police assume
警方怎会以为 纯粹的精神密友会密谋行凶?
that people in a platonic relationship
would want to murder someone?
警方怎会以为 纯粹的精神密友会密谋行凶?
um,during the test,they asked me some questions
那个测试 问了一些关于你的问题
about you and,um,us
and whether we had a relationship
关于我们是否认识，我承认了
and I said yes,because it's true.
And then they asked me something else,
他们还问了一些我措手不及的问题
something I hadn't considered.
Which was?
例如?
They asked meif I loved you.
他们问我是否爱你
What did you say?
你怎么说?
I said no.
我说不
But accordingto the polygraph,
但测谎仪显示，我撒谎了
that wasn't exactly true.
Well,I don't--I don't knowif that means anything.
我不知道这说明了什么
Polygraphs aren'tcompletely reliable.
那东西有时并不那么准确
I think perhaps the machine picked up on something,
也许是机器测出了一些东西
something that I wasn't aware of.
一些我没留意的东西
What's why I need you to take the test
所以你需要去做这个测试
and answer the detective's questions,
回答一些问题
because I'm not going to know exactly how I feel
我不知道我们将会怎样发展
until we put this behind us,but then,once we do...
除非我们可以解决这问题
we can move on.
- 只要解决了，那时...
can those chicorelli sisters dance or what?
我们需要大家 那些漂亮的甜姐儿们能跳舞吗
Wow,look out,broadway!
这里就是百老汇的大舞台
Now don't forget that we will have cookies and juice
我们还有曲奇和果汁
set up in the basement after we're done here.
早已为各位备妥
We want to see you all there.And for our next act,
希望大家不要离开
please welcome the musical stylings of julie and susan mayer.
接下来，是julie和susan mayer的声乐表演
I'll be right back.
我很快回来
Oh,um,I'm just gonna need a couple of seconds,
请各位耐心等待
so feel free to pray.
稍安无躁
Edie,the other day when I saw you making music with my family,
edie，我看见你和我家人 享受音乐的快乐时
I got a little jealousand I went a little crazy
我变得善妒和疯狂，
and I pushed you out.
所以我把你赶出门外.
Seeing you sitting here today,
今天你来捧场,
well,I can see how muchyou care about julie,
我可以知道你多在乎julie
and she comes first,
没什么比她更重要
and it should be you up thereplaying with her,not me.
我想与她同台的应该是你,不是我.
So I'm sorry.
- 我很抱歉
Thank you,susan.
谢谢，susan
How convenient that you decided this
我没带吉他随身
after I showed upwithout my guitar.
你这是明摆着让我难堪.
Well,like I said,I'm sorry.
我说过了，我很抱歉
I wish it could be youup there.
我只是希望你在台上
You know,I play piano.
你知道，我会弹钢琴
And so let's all welcome julie mayer
现在请欢迎julie和她的阿姨edie
and her aunt edie.
You did a good thing.
你做了件好事，
Yeah,well,I try.
是的，至少我尝试过
This thing has,like,90 flats in it.
让我歇一下 这东西很难摆弄
poor julie.
- 可怜的julie
Stop it. You're loving this.
- 算了吧，你幸灾乐祸
No,not at all
我没有
so they said you needed to see me.
他们说你要见我
What is it?What's goin' on?
怎么回事，发生了什么
Um,I've been thinking...
我一直在想
you know,about,um...
和john一起的事
everything that happened with john...
and...
和john一起的事
and,um...
我想我很自私，很愚蠢
I was really selfish and stupid.
And I'm sorry.
对不起
I really am sorry.
我真的感到很抱歉
That's all I had to say,really.
我只是想说这个
You know what?
你知道吗
That isthe best anniversary gift
这是你给我最好的周年纪念礼物
that you've ever given me.
Really?
- 真的？
Yeah.
是的
Actually,the one you gave meis really nice,too.
事实上你给我的也很不错
Everyone enjoys a game of make-believe now and then.
人们总喜欢偶尔自欺欺人
Of course,the ways in which we play can vary greatly.
每人的表达方式不尽相同
Sometimes we tell ourselves work won't interfere
有时我们觉得工作不会影响家庭
with our family life.
lynette,staff meeting,now.
lynette,准备员工会议，马上
Yeah.
Sometimes,we imagine certain relationships
我们总是幻想某段关系
to be more meaningful than they really are.
比实际的更加美好和意义深远
Occasionally,we put on a show,
有时我们掩饰不安
as if to convince ourselves our secrets
像是一切总在预算之中
aren't really all that terrible.
并不那么可怕
Yes,the game of make-believe is a simple one.
自欺欺人的游戏，人们乐在其中
Did you know rex van de kamp?
- 你认识vab de kamp
Yes.
是的
Did mrs. Van de kampask you to poison her husband?
是否rex vande kamp太太 指使你毒杀其丈夫
No.
没有
Did you poisonrex van de kamp?
你有否向其丈夫投毒？
You start by lying to yourself...
只要你说服自己谎言是真的
no.
没有
And if you can getothers to believe those lies...
你就可以让全世界相信这是真的
you win.
然后得到想要的一切